<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rage on Home Of Todfod</title>
    <link>http://todfod.xyz/categories/rage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rage on Home Of Todfod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021, todfod</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 20:57:45 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://todfod.xyz/categories/rage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>So Many People Love and Care for Me</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/so-many-people-love-and-care-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 20:57:45 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/so-many-people-love-and-care-for-me/</guid>
      <description>Politicians: Politicians never lie. They can never lie. Democracy protects us from politicians. Politicians are democratic. They are fighting for us. They built the bridges. They are fighting to get us vaccinated and healthy. They want the best for our children. They don&amp;rsquo;t engage in covert malaise, treachery, treason and can still keep a happy face. They are meant to rule us. We should submit to them. In the heats of summer I will stand in line to vote for my favorite politician who has vowed to increase oil exports from the arab states.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a Wonderful Life</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/wonderfullife/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 16:28:31 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/wonderfullife/</guid>
      <description>What is not real? What is real? How much of the surface of this myopian crackle is configurable? What can I believe on? What makes up faith? How trustworthy is the internet? Does things actually exist outside the screen? Do words have any meaning? Is there consensus for meaning? What makes up man? What makes up for memories? Do records need to exist? Does pain need to be hidden?
Is it future?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Light Is Better</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/yellow-light-is-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 20:30:09 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/yellow-light-is-better/</guid>
      <description>Yellow colored (above 3400k or so). White fluorescent is an abomination. Stop using it. It is unnatural. Natural morning light after sunrise is yellow. Daytime is yellow. Fucking evenings are &amp;hellip; you get the point. Stop making everything look so damn ugly with white light. Everything looks better in a yellow tint. The grand spread of using white light is probably a fucking kabal conspiracy at this point to turn the world into a concrete ridden satan sphere.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
