<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reading on Home Of Todfod</title>
    <link>http://todfod.xyz/tags/reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reading on Home Of Todfod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021, todfod renewed until 2022 by Pragyan Bimali</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 19:03:45 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://todfod.xyz/tags/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Beginnings of Moby Dick</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-beginnings-of-moby-dick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 19:03:45 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-beginnings-of-moby-dick/</guid>
      <description>But here is an artist. He desires to paint you the dreamiest, shadiest, quietest, most enchanting bit of romantic landscape in all the valley of the Saco. What is the chief element he employs? There stand his trees, each with a hollow trunk, as if a hermit and a crucifix were within; and here sleeps his meadow, and there sleep his cattle; and up from yonder cottage goes a sleepy smoke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Meditations</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/basedmarcus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 18:57:57 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/basedmarcus/</guid>
      <description>“Remember how long you’ve been putting this off, how many extensions the gods gave you, and you didn’t use them. At some point you have to recognize what world it is that you belong to; what power rules it and from what source you spring; that there is a limit to the time assigned to you, and if you don’t use it to free yourself it will be gone and will never return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten Soldier</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the_forgotten_soldier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 18:26:31 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the_forgotten_soldier/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;People who hated me would pursue me with vindictiveness, seeing in my past only cupidity and culpable error. Others might someday understand that men can love the same virtues on both sides of a conflict, and that pain is international.&amp;rdquo;
 -The Forgotten Soldier (Guy Sajer)
Now, what does the 19 year old Nazi say about the war? Hmmmm.
Read the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impetous Progress</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/impetous-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 18:45:55 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/impetous-progress/</guid>
      <description>There was a Nassim Taleb quote somewhere that said if one was not sure how tradition has continued for a long time chances were it continued because it was right and one should just leave it be. This nugget has been in the back of my mind ever since I heard it and saw things that were formed long ago that didn&amp;rsquo;t make sense to me just then but do so now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human, All to Human</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/human-all-to-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 19:41:47 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/human-all-to-human/</guid>
      <description>It is still a long way from this morbid isolation, from the desert of these experimental years, to that enormous, overflowing certainty and health which cannot do without even illness itself, as an instrument and fishhook of knowledge; to that mature freedom of the spirit which is fully as much self-mastery and discipline of the heart, and which permits paths to many opposing ways of thought. It is a long way to the inner spaciousness and cosseting of a super abundance which precludes the danger that the spirit might lose itself on its own paths and fall in love and stay put, intoxicated, in some nook; a long way to that excess of vivid healing, reproducing, reviving powers, the very sign of great health, an excess that gives the free spirit the dangerous privilege of being permitted to live experimentally and to offer himself to adventure: the privilege of the master free spirit!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
