<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>time on Home Of Todfod</title>
    <link>http://todfod.xyz/tags/time/</link>
    <description>Recent content in time on Home Of Todfod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021, todfod</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 19:02:56 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://todfod.xyz/tags/time/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Meditations</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/my-meditations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 19:02:56 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/my-meditations/</guid>
      <description>Time is the only tool and actual vessel you have for wealth building. Time functions as the line and various points across that line you find your goals and systems. Systems are always built around or in time. Knowledge expands with time. Experience nurtures with time. Wasting it is one big folly. Learning to respect it is one big virtue.
All time until yesterday is lost. What I know now comes from not throughout the twenty years that I I have been here but from fragments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In and Behind</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/in-an-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 17:40:14 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/in-an-behind/</guid>
      <description>The explorative worldview is a wonderful one to have. There is nothing more sincere and childish than blind exploration. Too sad most of us are willing to be in and behind a few pixels to really saviour the world for all its creations. Too bad that the Gods that you and I (used to) worship are of the most decadent kind.
A Triumph Over Rationality. That&amp;rsquo;s how I will describe the last few months of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Remember</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/i-remembered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 21:11:35 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/i-remembered/</guid>
      <description>One day while playing around in one of my previous schools before St. Xaviers, I hit my head in one of the lower edges of a slide and had to get a few stiches. I just happened to remember that moment today. These remembrances of things past haven&amp;rsquo;t been a rare occuring these past few months. . It is as if the place I came back to had a few tapes to show me of me and now that I remember these moments, the heart fills up with a shuddering uneasiness and a hint of vague nostalgia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
