<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>money on Home Of Todfod</title>
    <link>http://todfod.xyz/tags/money/</link>
    <description>Recent content in money on Home Of Todfod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021, todfod</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 19:34:19 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://todfod.xyz/tags/money/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Addresses</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/crypto-addresses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 19:34:19 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/crypto-addresses/</guid>
      <description>Time to fly to the moon. I know I am late to the party but here it goes if anyone wants to send me something for the blog.
BTC : bc1qcwu9zlyxmq0dhfkh65nncfy4tgjxgp7rcsy27l
XMR : 48g9PAavMpSf1WFbRs9jNGCj6BHShcTJSVZ8k2PH94iyBp89PCwDzWnNSbYiaqRfsiNhF5DmLZGWp4hANBB9gTHkEZWHgca</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Need Cashflow</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/why-you-need-cashflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 21:56:08 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/why-you-need-cashflow/</guid>
      <description>From the time I spent managing a Business that dealt with wholesale I saw what happens when cashflow sucks. And what happens is that you will slowly but surely go out of business.
If you have a business that relies on heavy credit from the consumer and the downpayment or payment constitues only a small part of the sales then that means the cashflow is fucked because you have less cash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Meditations</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/my-meditations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 19:02:56 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/my-meditations/</guid>
      <description>Time is the only tool and actual vessel you have for wealth building. Time functions as the line and various points across that line you find your goals and systems. Systems are always built around or in time. Knowledge expands with time. Experience nurtures with time. Wasting it is one big folly. Learning to respect it is one big virtue.
All time until yesterday is lost. What I know now comes from not throughout the twenty years that I I have been here but from fragments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is it Going?</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/hows_it-going/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 18:32:03 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/hows_it-going/</guid>
      <description>A tanking business. A ruined economy. Idiots and stupid IYI&amp;rsquo;s everywhere. A 50 km railway line. An unelected idiot in a elected place of business. A fragile heart. Virtue-signalling. Bigoteering. A college that will probably suck. A leaking roof for no reason. No money. Lots of money but nothing to do. Heat. Rain. Heat. Rain. A lockdown. A pandemic. Huge international organizations without much in terms of credibility or actual expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
