<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nepal on Home Of Todfod</title>
    <link>http://todfod.xyz/tags/nepal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nepal on Home Of Todfod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021, todfod</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 21:32:40 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://todfod.xyz/tags/nepal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Limitations Are Exciting</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/limitations-are-exciting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 21:32:40 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/limitations-are-exciting/</guid>
      <description>Limitations are exciting. Feeling limited boxes you in and innovation is born. The heart swings like a pendulum left and right but the limitation of communication makes sure I channel the energies elsewhere. I had instagram on for a few days. It&amp;rsquo;s alright, I just didn&amp;rsquo;t care much about it. Not for me. Though limitations can get exciting they are dreadfully boring. Life becomes stale. Stale turns to fulfilment once you let time ferment it enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There Is a Huge Conspiracy At Hand</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/there-is-a-huge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:26:07 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/there-is-a-huge/</guid>
      <description>There is a huge conspiracy brewing at hand. It has to do with printing materials. What are these materials? Licenses and passports. The license one is what concerns me the most so I will dwell on that more. I got my license around 15 months ago. Not the license per say but the piece of paper that acts as a license. A green piece of paper and a pink piece. I paid around two to three thousand rupees for the entire license registration process with expenses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Nation We Have</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-nation-we-have/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 20:57:30 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-nation-we-have/</guid>
      <description>In this land of all forsaken souls one finds himself trapped by the making of his own fate, the cultivation of his own values. Even after resolutely defining parameters and a stringent moral self-structure there is nothing more devastating to be destroyed completely not by better ideals to improve upon but a rotten core that hardly has ever achieved anything or created anything. Don&amp;rsquo;t believe me? Look around you. The asthetics you see, the corrupt nature of the soul that has shattered the pure beauty of all individual soul.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
