<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Home Of Todfod</title>
    <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Home Of Todfod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021, todfod</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 19:58:19 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://todfod.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Year One of Todfod</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/year-one-of-todfod/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 19:58:19 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/year-one-of-todfod/</guid>
      <description>In a couple of weeks todfod will be an year old. It has been a simple, quarantined year so far. I have told you some about my life updates.
At first todfod was thought of as a vessel for updating on life and other pursuits. It has done so wonderfully albeit things have been a bit vague. The theme has been switched up to add categories, SSL isn&amp;rsquo;t supported and there are images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Grandmother Smiled Like None Other</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/my-grandmother-smiled-like-none-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 21:27:54 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/my-grandmother-smiled-like-none-other/</guid>
      <description> Gayatri Devi Kafle.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Once There Was a Chair I Sat On</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/once-there-was-a-chair-i-sat-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 21:16:10 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/once-there-was-a-chair-i-sat-on/</guid>
      <description> Taken in the third floor of the Shrestha House where I rented a flat with two others.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Many People Love and Care for Me</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/so-many-people-love-and-care-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 20:57:45 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/so-many-people-love-and-care-for-me/</guid>
      <description>Politicians: Politicians never lie. They can never lie. Democracy protects us from politicians. Politicians are democratic. They are fighting for us. They built the bridges. They are fighting to get us vaccinated and healthy. They want the best for our children. They don&amp;rsquo;t engage in covert malaise, treachery, treason and can still keep a happy face. They are meant to rule us. We should submit to them. In the heats of summer I will stand in line to vote for my favorite politician who has vowed to increase oil exports from the arab states.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a Wonderful Life</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/wonderfullife/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 16:28:31 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/wonderfullife/</guid>
      <description>What is not real? What is real? How much of the surface of this myopian crackle is configurable? What can I believe on? What makes up faith? How trustworthy is the internet? Does things actually exist outside the screen? Do words have any meaning? Is there consensus for meaning? What makes up man? What makes up for memories? Do records need to exist? Does pain need to be hidden?
Is it future?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Less Sex</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/less-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 14:59:34 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/less-sex/</guid>
      <description>I find this Song the most pleasant to listen to.
I let it into my home, I let it into my home
Led a long way down, led a long way down
I let it in from the cold, I let it in from the cold
Led a long way down, led a long way down
I let it into my head, I let it into my head
Led a long way down, led a long way down</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Anecdote of Love</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/an-anecdote-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 14:29:58 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/an-anecdote-of-love/</guid>
      <description>Oh! how the times whisper. The gentle breezes form and swindle. Into bouquets of wonderous petals. The hours at hand are precious and ever so giving, ever so taking. Her eyes are of pearls made, her skin - the touch of snow.
I remember being struck without a warning, the ever flooding dam of love burst wide open without stop. The first stairs took to holding hands, slowly but surely to sharing bodies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ego Death</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ego-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 18:51:11 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ego-death/</guid>
      <description>The self exists and with it so does the ego.
Sometime during 2076 We were five of us. Teenage boys in the forest of Godavari. With quite a sizeable amount of psilocybin and no one to bother us. The initialization proccess was mild with weird twists in vision that slowly morphed to an entire twisting and turning of the physical form around us. All of us communicated that it was what we saw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tobacco and Tea</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/tobacco-and-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 20:11:54 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/tobacco-and-tea/</guid>
      <description>As I write these words there is a faint nicotine buzz in my head. Tobbacco can be fun but to be addicted to it would be quite a distaste for the body. But in moderation everything is alright. In moderation.
As I write this post I am in a vast expanse of tea plants and trees. The air is fresh. It smells of tea. There is a big beautiful tree across this small gentle stream and it is quite amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Addresses</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/crypto-addresses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 19:34:19 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/crypto-addresses/</guid>
      <description>Time to fly to the moon. I know I am late to the party but here it goes if anyone wants to send me something for the blog.
BTC : bc1qcwu9zlyxmq0dhfkh65nncfy4tgjxgp7rcsy27l
XMR : 48g9PAavMpSf1WFbRs9jNGCj6BHShcTJSVZ8k2PH94iyBp89PCwDzWnNSbYiaqRfsiNhF5DmLZGWp4hANBB9gTHkEZWHgca</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favourite Youtube</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/favourite-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 20:58:05 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/favourite-youtube/</guid>
      <description>It is time to consoooom content. Here are some I like.
Channels:
 Luke smith The New Pill I&amp;rsquo;m Not Norm  I can&amp;rsquo;t think of others at the moment. Sam Hyde&amp;rsquo;s content is spread across various channels. Also look at Charls World if you like.
Some videos I keep coming back to:
 Hyde talks about getting a skill Hyde talks about dealing with debt Tekwars + Hyde Luke says you&amp;rsquo;re not autistic 9/11 was a national tragedy  This is surface level web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackout</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/blackout/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 21:11:38 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/blackout/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned sometime past. Social media isn&amp;rsquo;t for me. I am off everything now. If I get a cheap VPS I will even be off google completly. Not a philosophical decision or anything, I just really love not giving a shit about people who I don&amp;rsquo;t give about. Heavy Emo. Plus this blog is better than all of those platforms combined. And I like writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Light Is Better</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/yellow-light-is-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 20:30:09 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/yellow-light-is-better/</guid>
      <description>Yellow colored (above 3400k or so). White fluorescent is an abomination. Stop using it. It is unnatural. Natural morning light after sunrise is yellow. Daytime is yellow. Fucking evenings are &amp;hellip; you get the point. Stop making everything look so damn ugly with white light. Everything looks better in a yellow tint. The grand spread of using white light is probably a fucking kabal conspiracy at this point to turn the world into a concrete ridden satan sphere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Need Cashflow</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/why-you-need-cashflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 21:56:08 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/why-you-need-cashflow/</guid>
      <description>From the time I spent managing a Business that dealt with wholesale I saw what happens when cashflow sucks. And what happens is that you will slowly but surely go out of business.
If you have a business that relies on heavy credit from the consumer and the downpayment or payment constitues only a small part of the sales then that means the cashflow is fucked because you have less cash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Big Symposium</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/one-big-symposium/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 19:11:21 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/one-big-symposium/</guid>
      <description>All of reality must be probably programmed. But the feeling that all of this is a symposium rather than a simulation is more fitting. Who is the conductor? Is he the one good gracious high above? Or the one terrible down below? Who has understood what is means to understand? Not you or me obviously.
What does the age of the phone, the internet, trump, climate change, quantitative easing tell us about this world?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Meditations</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/my-meditations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 19:02:56 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/my-meditations/</guid>
      <description>Time is the only tool and actual vessel you have for wealth building. Time functions as the line and various points across that line you find your goals and systems. Systems are always built around or in time. Knowledge expands with time. Experience nurtures with time. Wasting it is one big folly. Learning to respect it is one big virtue.
All time until yesterday is lost. What I know now comes from not throughout the twenty years that I I have been here but from fragments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beginnings of Moby Dick</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-beginnings-of-moby-dick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 19:03:45 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-beginnings-of-moby-dick/</guid>
      <description>But here is an artist. He desires to paint you the dreamiest, shadiest, quietest, most enchanting bit of romantic landscape in all the valley of the Saco. What is the chief element he employs? There stand his trees, each with a hollow trunk, as if a hermit and a crucifix were within; and here sleeps his meadow, and there sleep his cattle; and up from yonder cottage goes a sleepy smoke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Meditations</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/basedmarcus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 18:57:57 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/basedmarcus/</guid>
      <description>“Remember how long you’ve been putting this off, how many extensions the gods gave you, and you didn’t use them. At some point you have to recognize what world it is that you belong to; what power rules it and from what source you spring; that there is a limit to the time assigned to you, and if you don’t use it to free yourself it will be gone and will never return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like A Rolling Stone</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/likearollingstone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 18:53:15 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/likearollingstone/</guid>
      <description>By Bob Dylan
Link to the song here
Once upon a time you dressed so fine
You threw the bums a dime in your prime, didn&amp;rsquo;t you?
People&amp;rsquo;d call, say, &amp;ldquo;Beware doll, you&amp;rsquo;re bound to fall&amp;rdquo;
You thought they were all kiddin&#39; you
You used to laugh about
Everybody that was hangin&#39; out
Now you don&amp;rsquo;t talk so loud
Now you don&amp;rsquo;t seem so proud
About having to be scrounging for your next meal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten Soldier</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the_forgotten_soldier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 18:26:31 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the_forgotten_soldier/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;People who hated me would pursue me with vindictiveness, seeing in my past only cupidity and culpable error. Others might someday understand that men can love the same virtues on both sides of a conflict, and that pain is international.&amp;rdquo;
 -The Forgotten Soldier (Guy Sajer)
Now, what does the 19 year old Nazi say about the war? Hmmmm.
Read the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Providence</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/providence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 18:13:18 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/providence/</guid>
      <description>Once life starts its course of all available alternate timelines and possibilities and goes from one to the other like leper frogs swimming in the monsoon rains of Asar, nothing can be calculated. Nor anything be put into order as one wishes. There are too many ways to choose from. Too many avenues to take. All the while one could be better than the other. While the one you took could be the worst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impetous Progress</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/impetous-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 18:45:55 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/impetous-progress/</guid>
      <description>There was a Nassim Taleb quote somewhere that said if one was not sure how tradition has continued for a long time chances were it continued because it was right and one should just leave it be. This nugget has been in the back of my mind ever since I heard it and saw things that were formed long ago that didn&amp;rsquo;t make sense to me just then but do so now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In and Behind</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/in-an-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 17:40:14 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/in-an-behind/</guid>
      <description>The explorative worldview is a wonderful one to have. There is nothing more sincere and childish than blind exploration. Too sad most of us are willing to be in and behind a few pixels to really saviour the world for all its creations. Too bad that the Gods that you and I (used to) worship are of the most decadent kind.
A Triumph Over Rationality. That&amp;rsquo;s how I will describe the last few months of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Will Take Time</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/it-will-take-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 19:13:32 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/it-will-take-time/</guid>
      <description>If any one is reading this blog right now and are constantly checking on new updates and feel disappointed, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry but I have nothing of value to say on a regular basis. I derive value on what I find valuable and don&amp;rsquo;t find my words worthy of paper at this moment. I have been going through life as a test of one&amp;rsquo;s ability in action and I think I am actually getting good at it with an equal realization of my stupidity and inability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is it Going?</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/hows_it-going/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 18:32:03 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/hows_it-going/</guid>
      <description>A tanking business. A ruined economy. Idiots and stupid IYI&amp;rsquo;s everywhere. A 50 km railway line. An unelected idiot in a elected place of business. A fragile heart. Virtue-signalling. Bigoteering. A college that will probably suck. A leaking roof for no reason. No money. Lots of money but nothing to do. Heat. Rain. Heat. Rain. A lockdown. A pandemic. Huge international organizations without much in terms of credibility or actual expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limitations Are Exciting</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/limitations-are-exciting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 21:32:40 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/limitations-are-exciting/</guid>
      <description>Limitations are exciting. Feeling limited boxes you in and innovation is born. The heart swings like a pendulum left and right but the limitation of communication makes sure I channel the energies elsewhere. I had instagram on for a few days. It&amp;rsquo;s alright, I just didn&amp;rsquo;t care much about it. Not for me. Though limitations can get exciting they are dreadfully boring. Life becomes stale. Stale turns to fulfilment once you let time ferment it enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To the Limits</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/to-the-limits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 20:20:53 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/to-the-limits/</guid>
      <description>I am a practician. It&amp;rsquo;s all I want to be from now on. The world delves and masquerades itself in theory too much and the abstractions remain reflections of the masquerade rather than the real thing which it hopes to mirror or reflect. Rationality and being right don&amp;rsquo;t always stem from voracious theoretical manuscripts that purpose themselves to telling you how you should react and how you should think when the more rational and easier approach can be to find it, do it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There Is a Huge Conspiracy At Hand</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/there-is-a-huge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:26:07 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/there-is-a-huge/</guid>
      <description>There is a huge conspiracy brewing at hand. It has to do with printing materials. What are these materials? Licenses and passports. The license one is what concerns me the most so I will dwell on that more. I got my license around 15 months ago. Not the license per say but the piece of paper that acts as a license. A green piece of paper and a pink piece. I paid around two to three thousand rupees for the entire license registration process with expenses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making A New Home At Home</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/making-new-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 13:12:36 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/making-new-home/</guid>
      <description>I have decided to permanently move back to my home and possibly make my old home my new home for quite some time. I will probably enroll in one of the local colleges for a Economics degree and then do something on the side. My pursuit of a foreign education is over for now. The whole rigorous motif of going to some foreign place or a shithole like Kathmandu would be an unwise decision with these places showing pretty fragile outlooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Remember</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/i-remembered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 21:11:35 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/i-remembered/</guid>
      <description>One day while playing around in one of my previous schools before St. Xaviers, I hit my head in one of the lower edges of a slide and had to get a few stiches. I just happened to remember that moment today. These remembrances of things past haven&amp;rsquo;t been a rare occuring these past few months. . It is as if the place I came back to had a few tapes to show me of me and now that I remember these moments, the heart fills up with a shuddering uneasiness and a hint of vague nostalgia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Am I Sinking?</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/am-i-sinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 21:03:05 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/am-i-sinking/</guid>
      <description>Maybe I am. Maybe I am not. The next few weeks will tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Nation We Have</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-nation-we-have/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 20:57:30 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-nation-we-have/</guid>
      <description>In this land of all forsaken souls one finds himself trapped by the making of his own fate, the cultivation of his own values. Even after resolutely defining parameters and a stringent moral self-structure there is nothing more devastating to be destroyed completely not by better ideals to improve upon but a rotten core that hardly has ever achieved anything or created anything. Don&amp;rsquo;t believe me? Look around you. The asthetics you see, the corrupt nature of the soul that has shattered the pure beauty of all individual soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Theology</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/product-theology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 20:34:43 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/product-theology/</guid>
      <description> Don&amp;rsquo;t ask questions, just consume product and then get excited for next products.
  Jay Bauman of RedLetterMedia sums up the subject in one line.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fisherman</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-fisherman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 21:19:24 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-fisherman/</guid>
      <description>Although I can see him still—
The freckled man who goes
To a gray place on a hill
In gray Connemara clothes
At dawn to cast his flies—
It&amp;rsquo;s long since I began
To call up to the eyes
This wise and simple man.
All day I&amp;rsquo;d looked in the face
What I had hoped it would be
To write for my own race
And the reality:
The living men that I hate,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human, All to Human</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/human-all-to-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 19:41:47 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/human-all-to-human/</guid>
      <description>It is still a long way from this morbid isolation, from the desert of these experimental years, to that enormous, overflowing certainty and health which cannot do without even illness itself, as an instrument and fishhook of knowledge; to that mature freedom of the spirit which is fully as much self-mastery and discipline of the heart, and which permits paths to many opposing ways of thought. It is a long way to the inner spaciousness and cosseting of a super abundance which precludes the danger that the spirit might lose itself on its own paths and fall in love and stay put, intoxicated, in some nook; a long way to that excess of vivid healing, reproducing, reviving powers, the very sign of great health, an excess that gives the free spirit the dangerous privilege of being permitted to live experimentally and to offer himself to adventure: the privilege of the master free spirit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ojibwe</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ojibwe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 19:24:29 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ojibwe/</guid>
      <description> Sometimes I go about in pity for myself, and all the while A great wind carries me across the sky.
  -Ojibwe saying
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quasimodo</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/quasimodo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 10:46:02 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/quasimodo/</guid>
      <description>With all this death, hunger, killings in the name of nothing, dishonorable wars and people being blithering idiots in general nothing makes much sense anymore. You know Quasimodo predicted all of this. That guy huh.
Watch The Sopranos</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ramblings</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ramblings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 11:12:36 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ramblings/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Intellectual ideas are hard by to come these days&amp;rdquo; is such a zoomer-centric take. At least in my sphere of aquaintainces, something similiar of an idea seems to be a prevailing one. It also happens that the group of aquaintainces I am talking about think of themselves as &amp;lsquo;the shit&amp;rsquo; as the expression goes. Almost everyone shit talks and trashes others which is quite funny. The jokes that come of these conversations are pretty great and never fail to amuse me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
