<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on todfod.xyz</title>
    <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on todfod.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 18:57:57 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://todfod.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From Meditations</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/basedmarcus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 18:57:57 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/basedmarcus/</guid>
      <description>“Remember how long you’ve been putting this off, how many extensions the gods gave you, and you didn’t use them. At some point you have to recognize what world it is that you belong to; what power rules it and from what source you spring; that there is a limit to the time assigned to you, and if you don’t use it to free yourself it will be gone and will never return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like A Rolling Stone</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/likearollingstone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 18:53:15 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/likearollingstone/</guid>
      <description>By Bob Dylan
Link to the song here
Once upon a time you dressed so fine
You threw the bums a dime in your prime, didn&amp;rsquo;t you?
People&amp;rsquo;d call, say, &amp;ldquo;Beware doll, you&amp;rsquo;re bound to fall&amp;rdquo;
You thought they were all kiddin&#39; you
You used to laugh about
Everybody that was hangin&#39; out
Now you don&amp;rsquo;t talk so loud
Now you don&amp;rsquo;t seem so proud
About having to be scrounging for your next meal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Forgotten Soldier</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the_forgotten_soldier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 18:26:31 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the_forgotten_soldier/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;People who hated me would pursue me with vindictiveness, seeing in my past only cupidity and culpable error. Others might someday understand that men can love the same virtues on both sides of a conflict, and that pain is international.&amp;rdquo;
 -The Forgotten Soldier (Guy Sajer)
Now, what does the 19 year old Nazi say about the war? Hmmmm.
Read the book! Its a good book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Providence</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/providence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 18:13:18 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/providence/</guid>
      <description>Once life starts its course of all available alternate timelines and possibilities and goes from one to the other like leper frogs swimming in the monsoon rains of Asar, nothing can be calculated. Nor anything be put into order as one wishes. There are too many ways to choose from. Too many avenues to take. All the while one could be better than the other. While the one you took could be the worst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impetous Progress</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/impetous-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 18:45:55 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/impetous-progress/</guid>
      <description>There was a Nassim Taleb quote somewhere that said if one was not sure how tradition has continued for a long time chances were it continued because it was right and one should just leave it be. This nugget has been in the back of my mind ever since I heard it and saw things that were formed long ago that didn&amp;rsquo;t make sense to me just then but do so now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In and Behind</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/in-an-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 17:40:14 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/in-an-behind/</guid>
      <description>The explorative worldview is a wonderful one to have. There is nothing more sincere and childish than blind exploration. Too sad most of us are willing to be in and behind a few pixels to really saviour the world for all its creations. Too bad that the Gods that you and I (used to) worship are of the most decadent kind.
A Triumph Over Rationality. That&amp;rsquo;s how I will describe the last few months of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Will Take Time</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/it-will-take-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 19:13:32 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/it-will-take-time/</guid>
      <description>If any one is reading this blog right now and are constantly checking on new updates and feel disappointed, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry but I have nothing of value to say on a regular basis. I derive value on what I find valuable and don&amp;rsquo;t find my words worthy of paper at this moment. I have been going through life as a test of one&amp;rsquo;s ability in action and I think I am actually getting good at it with an equal realization of my stupidity and inability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hows it Going</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/hows_it-going/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 18:32:03 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/hows_it-going/</guid>
      <description>A tanking business. A ruined economy. Idiots and stupid IYI&amp;rsquo;s everywhere. A 50 km railway line. An unelected idiot in a elected place of business. A fragile heart. Virtue-signalling. Bigoteering. A college that will probably suck. A leaking roof for no reason. No money. Lots of money but nothing to do. Heat. Rain. Heat. Rain. A lockdown. A pandemic. Huge international organizations without much in terms of credibility or actual expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limitations Are Exciting</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/limitations-are-exciting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 21:32:40 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/limitations-are-exciting/</guid>
      <description>Limitations are exciting. Feeling limited boxes you in and innovation is born. The heart swings like a pendulum left and right but the limitation of communication makes sure I channel the energies elsewhere. I had instagram on for a few days. It&amp;rsquo;s alright, I just didn&amp;rsquo;t care much about it. Not for me. Though limitations can get exciting they are dreadfully boring. Life becomes stale. Stale turns to fulfilment once you let time ferment it enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To the Limits</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/to-the-limits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 20:20:53 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/to-the-limits/</guid>
      <description>I am a practician. It&amp;rsquo;s all I want to be from now on. The world delves and masquerades itself in theory too much and the abstractions remain reflections of the masquerade rather than the real thing which it hopes to mirror or reflect. Rationality and being right don&amp;rsquo;t always stem from voracious theoretical manuscripts that purpose themselves to telling you how you should react and how you should think when the more rational and easier approach can be to find it, do it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There Is a Huge Conspiracy At Hand</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/there-is-a-huge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 14:26:07 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/there-is-a-huge/</guid>
      <description>There is a huge conspiracy brewing at hand. It has to do with printing materials. What are these materials? Licenses and passports. The license one is what concerns me the most so I will dwell on that more. I got my license around 15 months ago. Not the license per say but the piece of paper that acts as a license. A green piece of paper and a pink piece. I paid around two to three thousand rupees for the entire license registration process with expenses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making A New Home At Home</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/making-new-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 13:12:36 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/making-new-home/</guid>
      <description>I have decided to permanently move back to my home and possibly make my old home my new home for quite some time. I will probably enroll in one of the local colleges for a Economics degree and then do something on the side. My pursuit of a foreign education is over for now. The whole rigorous motif of going to some foreign place or a shithole like Kathmandu would be an unwise decision with these places showing pretty fragile outlooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Remember</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/i-remembered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 21:11:35 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/i-remembered/</guid>
      <description>One day while playing around in one of my previous schools before St. Xaviers, I hit my head in one of the lower edges of a slide and had to get a few stiches. I just happened to remember that moment today. These remembrances of things past haven&amp;rsquo;t been a rare occuring these past few months. . It is as if the place I came back to had a few tapes to show me of me and now that I remember these moments, the heart fills up with a shuddering uneasiness and a hint of vague nostalgia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Am I Sinking?</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/am-i-sinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 21:03:05 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/am-i-sinking/</guid>
      <description>Maybe I am. Maybe I am not. The next few weeks will tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Nation We Have</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-nation-we-have/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 20:57:30 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-nation-we-have/</guid>
      <description>In this land of all forsaken souls one finds himself trapped by the making of his own fate, the cultivation of his own values. Even after resolutely defining parameters and a stringent moral self-structure there is nothing more devastating to be destroyed completely not by better ideals to improve upon but a rotten core that hardly has ever achieved anything or created anything. Don&amp;rsquo;t believe me? Look around you. The asthetics you see, the corrupt nature of the soul that has shattered the pure beauty of all individual soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Theology</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/product-theology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 20:34:43 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/product-theology/</guid>
      <description> Don&amp;rsquo;t ask questions, just consume product and then get excited for next products.
  Jay Bauman of Red Letter Media sums up the subject in one line.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Read</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/what-i-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 21:20:39 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/what-i-read/</guid>
      <description>These are all the books I have ever read and what I think about them. The authors or books are in no particular order.
  Kafka, Franz:
 The Trial : Read it when I was younger. Didn&amp;rsquo;t get the whole point across then but it slowly crept on. Intriguing writing. Fantastic scenes. Metamorphosis : A short read that is just perfect. I still go through pages of this book from time to time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fisherman</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-fisherman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 21:19:24 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/the-fisherman/</guid>
      <description>Although I can see him still—
The freckled man who goes
To a gray place on a hill
In gray Connemara clothes
At dawn to cast his flies—
It&amp;rsquo;s long since I began
To call up to the eyes
This wise and simple man.
All day I&amp;rsquo;d looked in the face
What I had hoped it would be
To write for my own race
And the reality:
The living men that I hate,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human, All to Human</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/human-all-to-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 19:41:47 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/human-all-to-human/</guid>
      <description>It is still a long way from this morbid isolation, from the desert of these experimental years, to that enormous, overflowing certainty and health which cannot do without even illness itself, as an instrument and fishhook of knowledge; to that mature freedom of the spirit which is fully as much self-mastery and discipline of the heart, and which permits paths to many opposing ways of thought. It is a long way to the inner spaciousness and cosseting of a super abundance which precludes the danger that the spirit might lose itself on its own paths and fall in love and stay put, intoxicated, in some nook; a long way to that excess of vivid healing, reproducing, reviving powers, the very sign of great health, an excess that gives the free spirit the dangerous privilege of being permitted to live experimentally and to offer himself to adventure: the privilege of the master free spirit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ojibwe</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ojibwe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 19:24:29 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ojibwe/</guid>
      <description> Sometimes I go about in pity for myself, and all the while A great wind carries me across the sky.
  -Ojibwe saying
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tired of the Circus</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/tired-of-the-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 11:13:37 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/tired-of-the-circus/</guid>
      <description>I have been thinking about democracy and the conclusion is that democracy is essentially bunk. Thank you Moldbug.
I heard Mr. Baburam was preaching about a directly elected president, removing Cholendra from office and all sorts of &amp;ldquo;great ideas&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s been pretty clear that Baburam is an idiot and nothing more than that.
What I don&amp;rsquo;t get about all of this is the still incessant praise for the idea of democracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quasimodo</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/quasimodo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 10:46:02 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/quasimodo/</guid>
      <description>With all this death, hunger, killings in the name of nothing, dishonorable wars and people being blithering idiots in general nothing makes much sense anymore. You know Quasimodo predicted all of this. That guy huh.
Watch The Sopranos</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ramblings</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ramblings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 11:12:36 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ramblings/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Intellectual ideas are hard by to come these days&amp;rdquo; is such a zoomer-centric take. At least in my sphere of aquaintainces, something similiar of an idea seems to be a prevailing one. It also happens that the group of aquaintainces I am talking about think of themselves as &amp;lsquo;the shit&amp;rsquo; as the expression goes. Almost everyone shit talks and trashes others which is quite funny. The jokes that come of these conversations are pretty great and never fail to amuse me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
