<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on Home Of Todfod</title>
    <link>http://todfod.xyz/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on Home Of Todfod</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021, todfod</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 14:29:58 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://todfod.xyz/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An Anecdote of Love</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/an-anecdote-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 14:29:58 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/an-anecdote-of-love/</guid>
      <description>Oh! how the times whisper. The gentle breezes form and swindle. Into bouquets of wonderous petals. The hours at hand are precious and ever so giving, ever so taking. Her eyes are of pearls made, her skin - the touch of snow.
I remember being struck without a warning, the ever flooding dam of love burst wide open without stop. The first stairs took to holding hands, slowly but surely to sharing bodies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ego Death</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ego-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 18:51:11 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ego-death/</guid>
      <description>The self exists and with it so does the ego.
Sometime during 2076 We were five of us. Teenage boys in the forest of Godavari. With quite a sizeable amount of psilocybin and no one to bother us. The initialization proccess was mild with weird twists in vision that slowly morphed to an entire twisting and turning of the physical form around us. All of us communicated that it was what we saw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tobacco and Tea</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/tobacco-and-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 20:11:54 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/tobacco-and-tea/</guid>
      <description>As I write these words there is a faint nicotine buzz in my head. Tobbacco can be fun but to be addicted to it would be quite a distaste for the body. But in moderation everything is alright. In moderation.
As I write this post I am in a vast expanse of tea plants and trees. The air is fresh. It smells of tea. There is a big beautiful tree across this small gentle stream and it is quite amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackout</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/blackout/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 21:11:38 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/blackout/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned sometime past. Social media isn&amp;rsquo;t for me. I am off everything now. If I get a cheap VPS I will even be off google completly. Not a philosophical decision or anything, I just really love not giving a shit about people who I don&amp;rsquo;t give about. Heavy Emo. Plus this blog is better than all of those platforms combined. And I like writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Big Symposium</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/one-big-symposium/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 19:11:21 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/one-big-symposium/</guid>
      <description>All of reality must be probably programmed. But the feeling that all of this is a symposium rather than a simulation is more fitting. Who is the conductor? Is he the one good gracious high above? Or the one terrible down below? Who has understood what is means to understand? Not you or me obviously.
What does the age of the phone, the internet, trump, climate change, quantitative easing tell us about this world?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Meditations</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/my-meditations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 19:02:56 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/my-meditations/</guid>
      <description>Time is the only tool and actual vessel you have for wealth building. Time functions as the line and various points across that line you find your goals and systems. Systems are always built around or in time. Knowledge expands with time. Experience nurtures with time. Wasting it is one big folly. Learning to respect it is one big virtue.
All time until yesterday is lost. What I know now comes from not throughout the twenty years that I I have been here but from fragments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Providence</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/providence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 18:13:18 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/providence/</guid>
      <description>Once life starts its course of all available alternate timelines and possibilities and goes from one to the other like leper frogs swimming in the monsoon rains of Asar, nothing can be calculated. Nor anything be put into order as one wishes. There are too many ways to choose from. Too many avenues to take. All the while one could be better than the other. While the one you took could be the worst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impetous Progress</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/impetous-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 18:45:55 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/impetous-progress/</guid>
      <description>There was a Nassim Taleb quote somewhere that said if one was not sure how tradition has continued for a long time chances were it continued because it was right and one should just leave it be. This nugget has been in the back of my mind ever since I heard it and saw things that were formed long ago that didn&amp;rsquo;t make sense to me just then but do so now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In and Behind</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/in-an-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 17:40:14 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/in-an-behind/</guid>
      <description>The explorative worldview is a wonderful one to have. There is nothing more sincere and childish than blind exploration. Too sad most of us are willing to be in and behind a few pixels to really saviour the world for all its creations. Too bad that the Gods that you and I (used to) worship are of the most decadent kind.
A Triumph Over Rationality. That&amp;rsquo;s how I will describe the last few months of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How is it Going?</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/hows_it-going/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 18:32:03 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/hows_it-going/</guid>
      <description>A tanking business. A ruined economy. Idiots and stupid IYI&amp;rsquo;s everywhere. A 50 km railway line. An unelected idiot in a elected place of business. A fragile heart. Virtue-signalling. Bigoteering. A college that will probably suck. A leaking roof for no reason. No money. Lots of money but nothing to do. Heat. Rain. Heat. Rain. A lockdown. A pandemic. Huge international organizations without much in terms of credibility or actual expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limitations Are Exciting</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/limitations-are-exciting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 21:32:40 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/limitations-are-exciting/</guid>
      <description>Limitations are exciting. Feeling limited boxes you in and innovation is born. The heart swings like a pendulum left and right but the limitation of communication makes sure I channel the energies elsewhere. I had instagram on for a few days. It&amp;rsquo;s alright, I just didn&amp;rsquo;t care much about it. Not for me. Though limitations can get exciting they are dreadfully boring. Life becomes stale. Stale turns to fulfilment once you let time ferment it enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To the Limits</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/to-the-limits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 20:20:53 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/to-the-limits/</guid>
      <description>I am a practician. It&amp;rsquo;s all I want to be from now on. The world delves and masquerades itself in theory too much and the abstractions remain reflections of the masquerade rather than the real thing which it hopes to mirror or reflect. Rationality and being right don&amp;rsquo;t always stem from voracious theoretical manuscripts that purpose themselves to telling you how you should react and how you should think when the more rational and easier approach can be to find it, do it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making A New Home At Home</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/making-new-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 13:12:36 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/making-new-home/</guid>
      <description>I have decided to permanently move back to my home and possibly make my old home my new home for quite some time. I will probably enroll in one of the local colleges for a Economics degree and then do something on the side. My pursuit of a foreign education is over for now. The whole rigorous motif of going to some foreign place or a shithole like Kathmandu would be an unwise decision with these places showing pretty fragile outlooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Remember</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/i-remembered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 21:11:35 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/i-remembered/</guid>
      <description>One day while playing around in one of my previous schools before St. Xaviers, I hit my head in one of the lower edges of a slide and had to get a few stiches. I just happened to remember that moment today. These remembrances of things past haven&amp;rsquo;t been a rare occuring these past few months. . It is as if the place I came back to had a few tapes to show me of me and now that I remember these moments, the heart fills up with a shuddering uneasiness and a hint of vague nostalgia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Am I Sinking?</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/am-i-sinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 21:03:05 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/am-i-sinking/</guid>
      <description>Maybe I am. Maybe I am not. The next few weeks will tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ramblings</title>
      <link>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ramblings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 11:12:36 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://todfod.xyz/posts/ramblings/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Intellectual ideas are hard by to come these days&amp;rdquo; is such a zoomer-centric take. At least in my sphere of aquaintainces, something similiar of an idea seems to be a prevailing one. It also happens that the group of aquaintainces I am talking about think of themselves as &amp;lsquo;the shit&amp;rsquo; as the expression goes. Almost everyone shit talks and trashes others which is quite funny. The jokes that come of these conversations are pretty great and never fail to amuse me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
